Guide to the Sarah Thomas papers,1996-2006.
Thomas, Sarah papers,1996-2006.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sarah Thomas papers, 1996-2006.
13-1-3599
Sarah E. Thomas
23.1 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Printed Materials, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alphabetical subject files documenting activities as Carl A. Kroch Cornell University Librarian relating to all aspects of administration.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Sarah Thomas came to Cornell in 1996 from the Library of Congress, where she held positions overseeing the library's public services, special collections and cataloging directorate. She was the Carl A. Kroch Cornell University Librarian and Under Thomas' leadership, the library continued to build its rare and special collections and embraced the digital age, developing a suite of online services and offering 24-hour worldwide access to a rich array of online journals and other electronic media. Thomas was the principal force behind Project Euclid, a Mellon Foundation-funded initiative to support the cost-effective online dissemination of mathematics and statistics journals. While at Cornell she served on the executive board of the Association of Research Libraries for six years and was its president in 2004-05. She also chaired the Digital Library Federation Steering Committee and was a member of the board of the Research Libraries Group.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Alphabetical subject files documenting activities as Carl A. Kroch Cornell University Librarian relating to all aspects of administration. Includes files relating to various digital initiatives, the opening of the Libe Cafe, the addition to Mann Library and renovations to many of the existing libraries and the building of a off-site high-density warehouse. Also, files documenting her professional involvement in organizations such as the executive board of the Association of Research Libraries, the Digital Library Federation Steering Committee and as a member of the board of the Research Libraries Group.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Thomas, Sarah E.; Association of Research Libraries.; Cornell University.Library.Project Euclid.; Digital Library Federation Steering Committee.; Research Libraries Group
Subjects:
Library administrators.; Library administrators.; Library buildings.; Library architecture.; Academic libraries--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Collection is restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Association of Academic Health Science Libraries (AAHSL), November 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AAU Working Group - LC Fellowships, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academic Assembly Steering Committee
  File retained by UL
- Academic Deans
- Academic Image of Exchange, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Academic Leadership Series, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  2 folders
- Access to Databases, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ACRL - Excellence in Academic Libraries Award, 2002, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
  4 folders
- ADS - Astrophysics Data System, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Adelson Library - Lab of Ornithology
- Administrative Board of Council, 2003-2004
- Administrative Charges, 2003
- Africana Library
- All Staff Meeting
- Alternatives Library, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Alumni Access, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13-16)
- Alumni Federation Speaker Series, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Amazon
- American Association of Publishers
- American Library Association, 1994-
- American Physical Association, 2006-
- Ameritech, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Annex, 2003-2004
- Annual Report
- Anti-Slavery, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Apple, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Architecture Materials, 2000-5 (Box 1, Folder 21-26)
  6 folders
- ARL
- ALCTS, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arms, Bill: D-Lib, 1999- (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ARTstor, 2005
- arXiv, 2004
- A and S Admissions, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Asia Collections, 2006
- Atlantic Philanthropic, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Backlog, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Bailey, Liberty Hyde, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Baker, Nicholson, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Betz, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Blackburn (Jeanne) Collection, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bloom, Harold, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bober, Natalie, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
- Book Collection, 2003
- Borrow Direct, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- Bruce, Tommy, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Budget Reductions, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Budget 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Budget 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Budget 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Budget, 2001- (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
- Cambodia, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Campaign Funding, 2005
- Capital Equipment, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Carnegie Mellon, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
- Cartmill, Lee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 27-28)
  2 folders; Budgets, Endowment Reports
- Case Studies, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Catalyst, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 30-35)
- CAU, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 36-39)
- Cause Award, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Center for the Built Environment and Urban Design, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Center for Natural Language Acquisition, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Center for Jewish History, 2000
- Center for Research Libraries, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4-8)
  5 folders
- Central Technical Services, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Cervantes Digital Library, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- China, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Christian Studies, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- CIDC, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
- CIDC - Oct. 5th, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- CIS, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- CIT, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
  3 folders
- CL3, 2005
- Classics, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- CLIR, 1996
  Look in box 20; 17 folders
- CLIR (Council on Lib. Info Resources), 2006
- Coalition for networked Information (CNI), 2006
- Cohen, Walter, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Collection Development, 2006
- Colorado State, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Columbia, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Common Spot, 2006
- Communication, 2006
- Commission on Preservation and Access, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Communications and Marketing Trustee Ad Hoc Comm., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Company of Biologists, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Compaq Laptops Proposal 11/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Competitive Staffs, etc., 2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Computer Science, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
- Computing and Info Science Task Force, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Conflict Interest, 2000-2006
- Consolidation, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Constitution Day, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Contracts/License Agreements, 1997
- Convenient Business Hours, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Cooke Library Budget Issues, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Copy, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Copyright, 2006
- Cornell Business Services, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Cornell Collection, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Cornell Digital Library, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Cornell Digital Press, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Cornell Institute for Social and Economic Research (CISER)
- Cornell University Masterplan, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Press, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3-8)
- Cornell University Press/CUL, 2004
- Council of Librarians, 2006
- Council of Scientific Society Presidents, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- CourseInfo, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Creation Station, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11-12)
- CTS Reorg, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- CUBIT, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- CUL Audit Report, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- CUL Correspondence, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- CUL Priorities, 2005-2007
- CUL Wide Committees, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Cybertown, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Daily Sun, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Copy of newspaper front page
- Dalton, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Database Contracts, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Delmas Foundation, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Digital Access Coalition, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Digital Archiving, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
- Digital Collections Framework, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Digital Futures, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 27-30)
- Digital Imaging, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Digital Preservation Policy Framework, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Digitization Service, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Disclosure Inc., 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Dissertations, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Distance Learning, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6-13)
  8 folders
- Diversity, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
- D-Lib, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- DLIT, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 17-22)
- DLF, 2006
- Document Delivery, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Dpubs, 2006
- DRA, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- D-Space, 2006
- Duke, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- EAD, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- East Asian Program, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Ebooks, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Ebsco, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- E Cornell, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
- Ehrenberg, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Electronic Dissertation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Electronic Publishing, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
- Electronic Records, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Electronic Reserves, 2006
- Elsevier, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Electronic Text Center, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- elincoln Prize, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- EMANI, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
- E - metrics, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- EMPSL Faculty Outreach, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Encompass, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Endeavor, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Endowed Libraries, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Endowment, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
- English Department, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 22-23)
- Engineering Library, 2006
- Enhancing Journal Access/Sciences, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Entomology Library, 2006
- E - Only, 2005
- Engineering/Atlanta, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- E - Reserves, 2006
- Ergonomics, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Esposito, Joe, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Euclid, 2006
- European Documentation Commission, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Events, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Exhibits, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 30-31)
- External Affairs, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Fabit, 2000
- Facilities Fact Sheet, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Fact Sheet - Sarah, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 2-6)
- Faculty Digitization Grants, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 7-13)
  7 folders
- Faculty Innovation in Teaching Grants Program, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Faculty Outreach Program, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- FCI, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Financial Plan, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Fine Arts Library, 2006
- Food and Drink Policy, 2001
- FPC Report, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Frick, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19-21)
- Frye Institute, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Future Libraries, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Gate Counts, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 24-26)
- Gateway, 1999
- Gay, Geri, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
- General Correspondence - Sarah Thomas, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Gentry, Robert, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Geneva Experiment Station Library, 1998
- German Project, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31-32)
- Getty Grant Program, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Gibran, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Gilder Lehrman Institute, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- GLOPAC, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- GLOPAD, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Google, 2006
- GPO Gov. Printing Office, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Grantmanship, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Grokker, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Grolier Club, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Gund, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Guns, Germs and Steel, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Harpers Magazine Foundation, 2007
- Harvard, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 3-6)
- HED/HEGIS, 1993-
  Look in box 21;34 folders
- Hewlitt, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
- Hillmann, Diane, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Hinchey, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Hiring Freeze, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- History Makers, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Hotel Library, 2003
- Holiday Card, 2006
- Human Resource Development Council, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Humanities, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
- Huntington Free Library, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 16-27)
  12 folders
- Huntington Free Library, 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1-18)
  18 folders
- Huron, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- IATUL, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- IBM Digital Library, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Iceland, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
- IFLA (International Federation of Library Associations), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
- ILL, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- ILO - International Labor Office, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- ILR Library, 2002
- Inclusion, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Indonesian Intern, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Information Management and Digital Libraries, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12-16)
- Integrated Framework, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Intellectual Property Committee, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Internal Grants, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 19-30)
- International Agreements, 2003- (Box 11, Folder 1)
- International Council of Archives, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Institute of Physics Publishing - IOPP, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- iPRES Conference, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- IRIS, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- IT Workforce Planning, 2005
- Ithaka, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Ivies Plus, 2006
- James Joyce Conference, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Janus Conference, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Jewish Studies, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Job Descriptions, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Johnson, Steve - Nov. 23rd, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Johns Hopkins National Adv. Council, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Journal Publishing Project, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Jones, Robert Trent, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- JSTOR, 2002
- Kanazawa, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kaplan, Michael, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Kaufman, Peter, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Kenney, Anne, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Kinkeldey, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19-20)
- Kirtas Technology Inc., 2006 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Knight Visual Resources, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Kroch Library Sprinkler System, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Kroch, Carl, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
- Kudos, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Lab/LIB, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Lafayette, 2006
- Lamport, Leslie, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Land Grant Mission Review, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Language/Learning Resource Center, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
- Large Scale Digitization, 2006
- Lavoisier, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Law Library, 2000
- Law Enforcement Access to Library Records, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- LC Mellon/CLIR Project, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Legislation, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Lehman, Jeffrey President, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
- Levenger Agreement, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Levy, David, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- LibQual, 2006
- Liber Architecture, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Library Admin Webpage, 2005
- Library Advisory Council, 2006
- Library Advisory Board, 2006
- Library Focus Group Transcripts, December 2000 (Box 24)
- LC Bicentennial Conference (Library of Congress), 2003 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Library Hi Tech Journal, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Library Hours, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Library Service Center, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Library of Congress, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Life Sciences, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Lithuania, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- LMS, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1-11)
  11 folders
- LMT, 2007
- Look Stationary, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Lorna Knight, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Luce, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Luster, Martin, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Lynching Collection, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Madison, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Maeda Asia Collection, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Making of America, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Management Institute, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20-22)
- Management Training Program, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Mann Library, 2006
- Margaret Mann, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Masterplan, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Math Conference, 2001
  Look in box 20; 1 folder
- Math Library, 2001
- McCarthy, Michael, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- McClure, Polley, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- McEneaney, Eamon, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Medical College Library, 2003
- Meier, Richard, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Mellon Foundation, 2006
- Memorial Sloan Kettering, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 30-32)
- Michigan Papryi, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Microsoft, 2006
- Million Book Ideas, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Minority Fellowship, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- MIT, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 36-38)
- Mittler, Elmar, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Models for Academic Support, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
- Morrison, Hedda, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Morrison, Toni, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Multimedia TF, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Murray, Tim, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Museum, Johnson Art, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Museum Licensing, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
- Music Library, 2000
- Myers-Briggs, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Nabokov, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- NAL - National Agricultural Library, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- NCITES - National Center for Info Transfer-Science, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- NDLF - National Digital Library Foundation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- NEH - National Endowment for the Humanities, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- NLM - National Library of Medicine, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Native American Collection, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Naxos, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- NCC/Japanese Library Resources, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- NERL, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Net Lib, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
- New Media Partnership, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Nomadic Computing, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- North Campus Library (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Northeast Research Librarians Consortium, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Noyes Collection, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- NSF, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Nua - Internet Security, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Numerical Recipe Books, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Nuremberg Papers, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- NYLINK, 2004
- NYPL - New York Public Library, 2004
- NYSHA - New York State Historical Association, 2006
- NYS Higher Education Initiative, 2006
- NYS Regents Commission on Library Services, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- NYSER Net, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- NYU - New York University, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- OCLC, 2007
- OECD - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Ohio State University, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Oklahoma Collection Development Conference, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Olin 201/IRIS Administration, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Olin Renovation, 2006
- O'Neill Trial, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Open Access, 2004
- Open Content Alliance, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Orientation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Organizational Charts, 1996-
- Otto Harrassowitz, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Outreach Program, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Outreach Performance Nominees, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Oya Rieger, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- PAC Network, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Packard Humanities Institute, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Parents Survey, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Patriot Act, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- PCCW, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Peer Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- PEW, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
- Photographs, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Picnics, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Physical Sciences Library, 1999
- Pingree, David, 2007
- Poland, Jean, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
- Pollex, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Portico, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Poros (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Preserving Digital Information, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- President's Council, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Press, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- PRI, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Primary Source, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Prism, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Procedure 13, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Program for Cooperative Cataloging, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Project 2000, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Project Harvest, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Promotion Review, 2006
- PSL Budget, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Public Port Committee, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Public Services Vision, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Publishing Research Quarterly, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Pub Med Central, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Qatar, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Race and Religion Portals, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Randel, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33-34)
- Rapid ILL, 2007
- Rare Manuscript Collections, 2006
- Rawlings, Hunter, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- RBDB, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Reaccreditation, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
- Recon, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
- Records Management, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Regional Depositories, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Reno, Janet, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Reorganization, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 44-47)
- Reserves, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Reuleaux, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- RLG, 2007
- Robinson Fund, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Rose Goldsen Archive, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
- Rosen, Bernard Carl, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Rothenberg, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
- Rubin Collection, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Sagan, Carl, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Salaries, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Sandler/Schmidt, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Sarah's Chron File, 2002-
  Look in box 19, 20 and 23; 33 folders
- Sarbanes Oxley, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Sarnoff, Dorothy, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Saylor, John, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Scholarly Communication, 2000
- Science Libraries, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Scientists - E-Papers, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- SCRLC, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Security, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
- SHOAH, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Skorton, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- SMET, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Smith, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 24-34)
- Song of the Vowels, 2004
- Space, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Sparc, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36-37)
- Speaker Series, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Springer Verlag (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Staff Directory, 1977- (Box 15, Folder 40-43)
- Staff Web, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Stamford Yacht Club, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Statistics (Box 16, Folder 3-52)
  50 folders
- Statistics Annual, 1989-
- Still Water Group, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Strategic Plans, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 54-55)
- Student Library Advisory Council, 2006
- SUNY Virtual, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Survey, 1993- (Box 17, Folder 2-37)
  36 folders
- Sustainable Workforce Proposal, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Syracuse 21st Century Award, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Tanner, Harold, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Task Force on Disposition, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Thailand, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Timbuktu Heritage Institute, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Tompkins County Library, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 7-13)
- To do lists (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Trethaway, Edward, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Tsinghua University, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Tyler, Jim, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Undergraduate Experience, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- United Way, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19-20)
- University Bylaws, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- University Council, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- University Faculty Senate Meetings, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- UMI, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- University of Illinois, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- University of Vermont, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Uportal, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- User Study, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28-30)
- Uris Family, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Uris Library, 1999
- Vet Library, 2005
- Vietnam, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Visitors, 1996-2005 (Box 18, Folder 33-39)
- Visual Resources Working Group, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- VIVO, 2006
- Vonnegut, Kurt, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Washington University, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Wason Collection, 2006
- WCMC-Q, 2006
- Webb, Jocelyn, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- WebFeat, 2006
- Weiss, Steven, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Wells College, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- West Campus, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
- Western Library Network, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- AD White Photographs, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Wireless, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Wisdom in the age of Dig. Info, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Wittenberg, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Womans Studies, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Wordsworth, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Letters to UL acknowledging additions to the collection
- Workforce Planning, 2003
  "Look in box 20; 11 folders; This section should be included with materials prev. removed from Sarah's office"
- Young, Perry Dean, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Zentralblatt, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Zentrum Fur Bucherhal Tung, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 18)